EPRIS BURNETT

WEB DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MOBILE

248.730.8645

EMAIL

eharrisburnett@gmail.com

LOCATION

Cornelius, NC

ESDHB0906.GITHUB.IO | LINKEDIN.COM/IN/EPRISHB

Recently switched to front-end development after being a Graphic Designer for over 10 years. Beginning experience in front-end web development with a concentration on React. Customers are first as happy and well-informed customers drive results. Agile and goal-oriented worker believing in beating deadlines, not meeting them.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BROOKS EQUIPMENT

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT
Web Developer & Graphic Designer
Charlotte, NC Aug 2018

- Perform web maintenance on 7 company sites, including making older sites mobile-friendly, optimized for search engines and redeveloping when UI is updated
- Increased web traffic by 6 7% by implementing fundamental SEO strategy alongside the marketing team
- Assist graphic designers with heavy workloads by creating web banners, optimizing images for web, and developing catalogs and deliverables to keep customers informed

BOY SCOUTS OF AMERICA

ADVERTISING

Graphic Designer | Charlotte, NC Aug 2018

- Maintained design consistency in sales sheets
- Created ads for Scout Shops promotional events
- Developed banners and flyers for kits

BRADLEY CO.

PROMOTIONAL MERCHANDISING

Graphic Designer Southfield, MI May 2017 - 2018

- Managed up to 20+ projects simultaneously, including rush orders, with deadlines of 24 hours or less
- Created presentations for web store advertisement banners for various clients
- Curated email blasts for PPG Paint yearly calendars via MailChimp and Illustrator

APPLET SOCIAL

WEB & APP DEVELOPMENT Project Manager Detroit, MI Sep 2014 - 2018

- Managed multiple projects and organized team communication via Podio project management system
- Utilized HTML/CSS in conjunction with ShoutEm to produce apps

CONTINENTAL SERVICES

DINING & CATERING

Graphic Designer Troy, MI Sep 2012 - 2014

- Developed and managed branding across 7 venues
- Collaborated with cafe managers and web designer to ensure proper promotion of products and sales increase
- Successfully launched digital menu boards in over 5 cafe locations including General Motors and Mercedes Benz Financial Center

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, React

Web: HTML/CSS, Responsive Web Design,

Accessibility

Framework/Libraries: Bootstrap, Material UI, Framer, React Hooks Forms, Styled Components Adobe Creative Cloud: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, XD, Dreamweaver, After Effects, Acrobat, Lightroom

OS: Windows, Linux, Mac

PROJECTS

Memory Game (JavaScript)
Feed Reader Testing (Jasmine)
My Reads (React)
Neighborhood Map (React)

EDUCATION

2018 - Current

BACHELORS OF ART

*GRAPHIC DESIGN*Southern New Hampshire University
Manchester, NH

2018

NANODEGREE

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT Udacity Online